rocketmiles.com 2015-09-19

# Rocketmiles - Privacy Policy

The policy was last modified on July 23rd, 2013

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

Rocket Travel, Inc. ("Rocket Travel", "we", "us") knows that you care about how information about you is used and shared, and wants you to feel safe online. For that reason, we want to let you know how we treat personal information that we collect from users of both the full and mobile versions of our web site www.rocketmiles.com (together, the “Rocket Travel Site”). We also describe the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. By providing personal information through the Rocket Travel Site you explicitly agree to our collection and use of all such information as described in this privacy policy.

## What information we gather and use

When you use the Rocket Travel Site or the booking or other services available through the Rocket Travel Site, you may provide certain personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, telephone number, mailing address, credit card number or similar information.

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to automatically register an account with us. Services like Facebook Connect may give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us using the information listed below.

Some of the personally identifiable information we receive from you is needed to set up your account, submit content, and transmit your reservation information to a travel partner. If you access the Rocket Travel Site from a mobile device, we may also gather geographic location information from you, to better customize your experience using the Rocket Travel Site.

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

## How we use and share information

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone without your permission. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our business, processing credit card transactions or otherwise conducting our business, or providing services to you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process, enforce Rocket Travel Site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. If Rocket Travel is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,

We share and use the information we collect in the following ways:

  * _To personalize your experience:_ Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * _To improve our website:_ We continually strive to improve our offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * _To improve customer service:_ Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * _To process transactions:_ Specifically, your information will be shared with hotels and other travel partners to process transactions made on the Rocket Travel Site, and to third party providers of credit card transaction.
  * _To send periodic emails:_ The email address you provide for order processing will be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. We may also email you about specials and promotions offered through our Site.

## How we protect your information

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your credit card number(s) will not be stored on our servers, unless your reservation type requires us to forward such information to the hotel provider. Any credit card numbers are processed and stored in a PCI compliant manner.

## Use of cookies and other tracking technologies

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. We use session and persistent cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and understand and save your preferences for future visits. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly.

We partner with third party ad networks to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

The use of tracking technologies by our service providers, technology partners or other 3rd party assets (such as social media) on the site is not covered by our privacy policy. These 3rd parties may use cookies, clear gifs, images, and scripts to help them better manage their content on our site. We do not have access or control over these technologies. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personally identifiable information.

## Updating and correcting information

We encourage you to promptly update your personally identifiable information if it changes. You may correct, update, amend, remove, or ask to have it removed by making the change on your user account settings page, by emailing our Customer Support at concierge@rocketmiles.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. If you no longer desire our service, please contact us directly. We will respond to your request within 30 days. However, because we keep track of past transactions, you cannot delete information associated with your past transactions on the Rocket Travel Site, nor can we delete information included in our back-up files.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter or other promotional email, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at concierge@rocketmiles.com

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of the Rocket Travel Site may make any changes to their information at anytime by contacting us at concierge@rocketmiles.com or Rocket Travel, Inc., 22 Fells Road, Winchester, MA 01890. Please be sure to include your full name, address, email address and specifically what type of information you do not want to receive. Please allow up to 6 to 8 weeks to process your request from the date of receipt.

## Links to other sites

The Rocket Travel Site may contain links to other sites (including those embedded in advertisements) over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy at any site you visit.

Our Web site also includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, links to our various social media pages and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Site at /terms

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

Our Web site also includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, links to our various social media pages and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

    Rocket Travel, Inc.
    560 W Washington
    Chicago, IL 60661
    Email: concierge@rocketmiles.com
